[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_122",
        "question": "A 34 year old woman presents to clinic complaining of a painful, red spot on the left shoulder that developed about 4 years ago. <br>- She denies any trauma that may have incited it. <br>- It has been evaluated by multiple dermatologists and treated with intralesional corticosteroid injections, but it continues to enlargen and has become more raised. <br>-   Physical examination reveals a multilobular violaceous, poorly demarcated firm plaque that is tender to palpation on the left shoulder. <br>- Histopathologic analysis of the lesion reveals lesional cells that stain positive for CD34 and negative for Factor 13a.",
        "option1": "Dermatofibrosarcoma protuberans",
        "option2": "Keloid",
        "option3": "Dermatofibroma",
        "option4": "Squamous cell carcinoma",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "57%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_054",
        "question": "A 43-year-old elementary school teacher presents with a rash that began on his left thigh approximately 4 months earlier; the rash has since spread. <br>- It is mildly itchy but has no associated pain or bleeding. <br>- His past medical history is significant for allergic rhinitis and atopic dermatitis. <br>- Suspecting eczema, he has been applying an over-the-counter hydrocortisone 1% cream as well as a moisturizer, which transiently alleviates the itch. <br>- He has not changed laundry or hygiene products. <br>- On physical examination, there are slightly erythematous, minimally scaly patches scattered over his left hip and buttock.",
        "option1": "Levamisole-induced antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody vasculitis",
        "option2": "Tinea incognito",
        "option3": "Cutaneous lupus",
        "option4": "Eczema",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "74%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_045",
        "question": "A 45-year-old woman with insulin-dependent diabetes mellitus presents with a sore on her right leg. <br>- She describes a long-standing history of asymptomatic lesions on her shins but had only recently injured her leg, causing the sore, which is slow to heal. <br>- Despite a 15-year history of diabetes, she has no systemic complications. <br>- She has large, well-circumscribed plaques on her anterior shins bilaterally, which are yellow-brown with telangiectasias and minimally violaceous borders.",
        "option1": "Necrobiosis lipoidica",
        "option2": "Necrobiotic xanthogranuloma (NXG)",
        "option3": "Acquired digital fibrokeratoma (ADFK)",
        "option4": "Diabetic dermopathy",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "88%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_064",
        "question": "A man, aged 68 years, with no known history of atopy presents with a 4-month history of an itchy and burning rash on the legs that has been recurring every winter for the past 3 years. <br>- He notes that he had dry skin at baseline and did not use emollients, but he did try hydrocortisone 1% cream without improvement. <br>- Examination revealed ovoid, erythematous, well-marginated plaques on the lower legs and dorsal feet with variable scaling and focal weeping and crusting. <br>- There were no nail changes, and the rest of his skin examination was notable only for xerosis.",
        "option1": "Psoriasis",
        "option2": "Bullous impetigo",
        "option3": "Tinea corporis",
        "option4": "Nummular dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_131",
        "question": "A 35-year-old man with a past medical history of obesity and tobacco use presents to clinic with a seven month history of boils under the arms and in the groin. <br>- He reports that the boils come up twice a week under the arms, and once a week in the groin. <br>- The individual boils are painful and will often drain foul odorous yellow green material. <br>- Many of the boils have been drained in the emergency room. <br>-   Physical examination reveals multiple painful, tender subcutaneous nodules draining yellow-white malodorous pus in the bilateral axilla and inguinal folds. <br>- Scattered double headed comedones are present with few sinus tracts noted.",
        "option1": "Abscesses",
        "option2": "Inflamed sebacous cysts",
        "option3": "Impetigo",
        "option4": "Hidradenitis suppurativa ",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "83%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_059",
        "question": "A 48-year-old premenopausal woman, who has had one pregnancy and has delivered once, presents with a 15-month history of left breast deformity. <br>- The patient began having pain in the region 2 months ago. <br>- A review of systems is negative for weight loss, fever, or nipple discharge. <br>- Her medical history is otherwise unremarkable, and her family history is noncontributory. <br>- Physical examination is notable for extensive left nipple inversion and retraction, a large underlying mass in the central breast, edema and ulceration of the overlying skin of the breast, and matted ipsilateral axillary nodes. <br>- There is no erythema of the skin. <br>- The right breast is unremarkable.",
        "option1": "Congenital nipple inversion",
        "option2": "Nipple inversion secondary to neglected malignancy",
        "option3": "Duct ectasia",
        "option4": "Periductal mastitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_083",
        "question": "A 33-year-old Black man presents to a dermatology clinic with a 5-month history of asymptomatic lesions on his arms and trunk. <br>- He is otherwise healthy with no personal or family history of skin disease. <br>- He has no history of fever, cough, shortness of breath, or joint pain. <br>- The patient has not tried any treatments for these lesions. <br>- On examination, there are several smooth, well-demarcated hypopigmented plaques on his upper arms and left flank. <br>- He has no similar lesions elsewhere on his body.",
        "option1": "Fungal infection",
        "option2": "Cutaneous lupus",
        "option3": "Cutaneous sarcoidosis",
        "option4": "Rosacea",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "92%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_034",
        "question": "A 44-year-old woman presents for her annual full skin examination. <br>- She has a specific concern regarding a lesion on her left lower leg. <br>- She recalls having a mosquito bite in that area a few years earlier, but it never went away. <br>- The lesion is bothersome only when she shaves her legs and nicks it; otherwise, there is no associated pain or tenderness. <br>- Physical examination reveals a firm, flat, pink and brown nodule located on the left anterior proximal shin. <br>- The lesion dimples inward when pressure is applied.",
        "option1": "Dysplastic nevi",
        "option2": "Dermatofibroma",
        "option3": "Basal cell carcinoma",
        "option4": "Keloids",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "57%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_081",
        "question": "A 15-year-old girl presents with patches of hair loss on her scalp that have been present for the last 6 months. <br>- She reports that her scalp is not itchy or painful and denies any recent illnesses, diet changes, or stressful life events. <br>- She does not have any other medical conditions and takes no medications. <br>- Her uncle had a similar condition that started when he was in his 20s, but no one else in the family has experienced hair loss. <br>- The patient says she has not tried any treatments for the condition. <br>- On examination, she has several well-demarcated patches of hair loss on her frontal and parietal scalp, with no perifollicular erythema or scale.",
        "option1": "Alopecia areata",
        "option2": "Androgenetic alopecia",
        "option3": "Tinea capitis",
        "option4": "Trichotillomania",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_042",
        "question": "A healthy 45-year-old woman presents with a several-month history of a small papule at the corner of her right eye. <br>- The lesion is asymptomatic and is not enlarging, but she has cosmetic concerns. <br>- She denies diplopia, vision loss, or any other lesions on her face and body. <br>- Examination reveals a dome-shaped, smooth, translucent papule filled with watery fluid located below the lateral canthus of her right eye.",
        "option1": "Mucous retention cysts",
        "option2": "Warthin tumors",
        "option3": "Hidrocystomas",
        "option4": "Cystic pleomorphic adenomas",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "65%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_025",
        "question": "An 8-year-old African-American boy presents with a 3-day history of fever, pain, and a rash on his trunk. <br>- On examination, the patient has several fragile, bullous lesions on his trunk, many of which have eroded, exposing erythematous, annular lesions. <br>- The patient is febrile and shaking in the office, and he appears to be in pain. <br>- He has no other relevant social or family history and does not take any medications. <br>- His mother is very concerned about her son.",
        "option1": "Bullous impetigo",
        "option2": "Bullous erythema multiforme",
        "option3": "Autoimmune bullous dermatoses",
        "option4": "Stevens-Johnson syndrome",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "82%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_139",
        "question": "A 22-year-old female presents with a brown rough spot on the left shin which she noted when shaving her leg. <br>- She thinks it may have been there for a few weeks. <br>- She denies any pain, pruritus, or spontaneous bleeding from the site. <br>- She cannot recall any trauma that may have caused the lesion. <br>-  She denies any personal or family history of skin cancer. <br>-   Physical exam reveals a thin, firm brown dome shaped papule on the left shin that invaginates upon pinching.",
        "option1": "Fibrous papule",
        "option2": "Keratoacanthoma",
        "option3": "Dermatofibroma",
        "option4": "Keratosis pilaris",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "86%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_046",
        "question": "A 60-year-old man presents with rapidly growing lesions on his face, trunk, axillae, flexural areas, and groin. <br>- The lesions appeared 3 months earlier in his perianal area and extended rapidly to other areas. <br>- Previously, he was treated with topical agents for atopic dermatitis and seborrheic dermatitis without improvement. <br>- Examination reveals disseminated violaceous papules and plaques on the face, trunk, axillae, and perianal area; some lesions were confluent and ulcerated. <br>- Yellowish-red to skin-colored papules are present on the scalp. <br>- He has no palpable lymphadenopathy or organomegaly.",
        "option1": "Cutaneous Langerhans cell histiocytosis",
        "option2": "Prurigo nodularis",
        "option3": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "option4": "Atopic dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "45%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_126",
        "question": "A 45-year-old man with a past medical history of hypertension presents with concerns of a rash on his left lower back that his wife noticed two days ago. <br>- The rash has been progressively enlargened. <br>- Patient denies any pain or any prior treatments. <br>- He thinks the surrounding skin is warm and may be infected, but he denies any drainage. <br>-  He reports that they went hiking eight days ago in Rhode Island. <br>-   Physical exam demonstrates a non-scaly large annular, pink-red patch on the left lower back with a bright pink center and clear central clearing.",
        "option1": "Syphilis ",
        "option2": "Erythema migrans",
        "option3": "Psoriasis ",
        "option4": "Tinea corporis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "92%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_005",
        "question": "A 29-year-old woman with a history of acne presents to the clinic with 3 discrete, atrophic, blue-tinged plaques on her face. <br>- The plaques were located on her forehead and cheeks bilaterally. <br>- The patient states the lesions had been present for several months and had slowly worsened until they stabilized at their current appearance. <br>- The patient reported that the lesions occurred after she went to a physician for “acne treatment.” The patient has no other medical conditions or relevant social history.",
        "option1": "Pityriasis rosea",
        "option2": "Corticosteroid-induced atrophy",
        "option3": "Lichen sclerosis",
        "option4": "Morphea",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "79%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]